Guide to the George and Katy Abraham Papers, 1915-2005
Abraham, George and Katy papers.
- Series I. Africa
  - Photographs
    - Soldiers playing baseball, native woman with child (Box 2, Folder 205)
    - Black and white military baseball game, chimp, native boats, building (Box 2, Folder 206)
    - US Military funeral, chimp circus St. Louis postcard, native women (Box 2, Folder 207)
    - Military services map, Liberia to Asmara route (Box 2, Folder 208)
    - Machine gunner, landscape scenes, street scene (Box 2, Folder 209)
    - Outdoor woodshop (Box 2, Folder 210)
    - Camp with wire fence, print of drawing by Kay Wiest (Box 2, Folder 211)
    - Doc A.,Doc A and friend, misc. (Box 2, Folder 212)
    - Black American troops on boat (Box 2, Folder 213)
    - Chimp drinking from cup, camel's head, African military band (Box 2, Folder 214)
    - Black US troops arriving on boat, Army baseball game (Box 2, Folder 215)
    - "First American Negro Soldier" to set foot in Liberia (Box 2, Folder 216)
    - Chow line, soldiers, native war exercise (Box 2, Folder 217)
    - Black soldiers disembarking, Atumpom drawing, dignitaries, boat scene (Box 2, Folder 218)
    - Plane landing, painted native women dancing (Box 2, Folder 219)
    - African albino woman (Box 2, Folder 220)
    - War progeny, children, integration (Box 2, Folder 221)
    - Home of 300 Africans (Shangri-La camp) (Box 2, Folder 222)
    - Pyramid, native women dancing (Box 2, Folder 223)
    - Painted native women dancing (Box 2, Folder 224)
    - Native girls dancing, "Paradise Girls" (Box 2, Folder 225)
    - Dejected young woman (Box 2, Folder 226)
    - Painted native women (Box 2, Folder 227)
    - Native women dancers (Box 2, Folder 228)
    - Painted native women dancing (Box 2, Folder 229)
    - Painted native women (Box 2, Folder 230)
    - Painted native women, "Army-hired prostitutes" (Box 2, Folder 231)
    - Snake bitten man (Box 2, Folder 232)
    - Medical corps, snake catching unit (Box 2, Folder 233)
    - Snake catching unit official photograph (Box 2, Folder 234)
    - Street snake charmer with two cobras (Box 2, Folder 235)
    - Black mamba (Box 2, Folder 236)
    - Python, India (Box 2, Folder 237)
    - Snakes (Box 2, Folder 238)
    - Man with snake, Billy O, native woman, two men (Box 2, Folder 239)
    - Snake and snake-bitten finger (Box 2, Folder 240)
    - Python in India (Box 2, Folder 241)
    - Indian snake man (Box 2, Folder 242)
    - Medical snake catching man with two snakes (Box 2, Folder 243)
    - Native 'military police' drilling (Box 2, Folder 244)
    - Native MP training (Box 2, Folder 245)
    - Black Platoon marching (Box 2, Folder 246)
    - Mortar training of Africans (Box 2, Folder 247)
    - Cargo ships, scuttled axis ship, landscape, medicine man (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Native band, native blacksmiths (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Message drum (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Country Devil dance/play (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Street scene, talking drum (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Native men with guns, Atta's funeral ceremony (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Africans celebrating death of Sir Atta (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - King Atta memorial scene (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Native chief/king memorial statue (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Five young boys with drums, US Amphibious plane (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Native woman scarred facial markings (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Native man dancing, ceremonial witch doctor (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Men making knives (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Painted women dancing, quarry work, women with baskets on head (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Nigerian merchant (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Sailboat, Africans, Farmington River, Liberia (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Native blacksmith (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Attendant purifies air for native country devil (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Woman making country soap (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Death celebration, Akyea Mensah (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Eritrean laundry (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Africans gambling (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Market scene, Accra (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Costumed country devil (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Native executioners (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Country devil in haystack (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Native country devil with boy (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Native Merry Christmas (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Talking drums honoring dead Chief Atta (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Central African merchant with bowls (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Dance of the Virgins (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Three native women making foo-foo (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Country devil dance (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - African witch doctor (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Native scene, three women and two children; game; building; sphinx (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Building, military flag raising, African women, native boys (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Native men and boys, mountain scene (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Native group, man with camel, cable car, passenger train car (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Typical scenes from Central Africa (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Africans cleaning, North African desert (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - African women, one with knife (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Young native girl (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Maiduguri, Nigerian village (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Women with babies, Mosque (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Native group scenes, street with buildings (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Building construction (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Liberian woman with child (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Central African beggars (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Americanized native woman, two street scenes, soldiers on horses (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Two Africans fishing with baskets (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Native washing clothes, "Blue Monday" (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Young native girl, cargo ship (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Native Africans (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Dance of the Virgins (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Native women (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Talking Charlie and his wife - one of them (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Bassa (native) bush girls (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Native bush women - Bassa tribe, Liberia (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Four women nursing babies, Gold Coast (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Two native women bathing (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Africans fueling, scuttled Axis ship (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Man and boy pouring into large can, Banda Abissina, birds (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Africans, West Africa (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Africans, Central Africa (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Native woman with bra (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Seven men with machetes (ceremonial) (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Nigerian native girl - scarred face (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Native woman with child (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Young native woman (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Old native woman, heavily wrinkled (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Woman pounding food, river and street scenes (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Grain market, Asmara, Eritrea (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Native woman with child, painted face and scars (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Native girl (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Native woman carrying firewood, Eritrea (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Native persons, trolley on bridge, native bull session, Asmara (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Native scenes, pots (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Horseman with cattle, painted native woman (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Native sailing on river (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Africans walking on road, bridge/wall scene (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Young native girl (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - US man with young native woman (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Native man in straw hat (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - African drummer, native group scene (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Large native group, giraffes (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Native group scene, Kay M. Wiest drawing of snafu dock (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Pulling in fishnet, Gold Coast (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Native girl with compact (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Plowing a field, Eritrea (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Native, Central Africa (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Africans with machetes and rifles (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Boat building, coils of rope; native girl with skin disorder/scars (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Street produce scene, two native women (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Three native women with painted faces and dresses (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Africans building a hut (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Monkey bridge river scene, Liberia (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Native village scene (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Native mourners of Sir Afori Atta (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Native women doing laundry, Shangri-La camp (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Africans drumming (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Native woman sifting/winnowing rice (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Celebrating the African way (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Native women weaving crab net (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Native woman with child and fish traps (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Native man with scarred face, Italian officer memorial (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Preliminary stages of clitoris operation (ceremonial) (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Native girls before devil bush cutting operation (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Sex organ cutting ceremony, native masks (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Bassa tribe girl prepared for puberty rites (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Vaginal operation, before and after (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Bush girl after cliterodectomy (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Preparing girls for clitoris operation (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Detailed photos of cliterodectomy (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Three young acrobats from snake society (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Snake society acrobatics (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Snake society tumblers (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Snake society, freighter ship, landscape, dog urinating on Nazi helmet (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Snake society, scuttled Axis ship (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Two young boys, snake society (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Snake society acrobatics (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Snake society, acrobatics with knives, snakes (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Snake society acrobatics (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Woman with tribal marking, snake society (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Native men and boys, snake society (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Snake society men, two native women dancing (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Photo Negatives
    - Negatives of photos, mostly Africa: chicken on roller skates, Billy O with pipe, Christmas card photo, family photos, miscellaneous flora, fauna and landscapes (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - African medical (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - African medical, elephantiasis (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - African bush men (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - South African snake corps (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Indian snake charmers (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Snakes (Box 4, Folder 6-7)
    - Chimps, monkeys (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
    - George Abraham family (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Loose negatives, Africa (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - African drums (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Loose negatives, Africa (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Female Africans, Liberia (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Basket weavers, Kano, Nigeria (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Ebony effigy of Sir Afori Atta, funeral feast (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Christianburg castle, Accra, Gold Coast (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Scenery shots (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Sweater girls, Liberia (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Native shipscraper (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Native worker, Firestone plantation, Liberia (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - African tumblers, Liberia (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - President Tubman parading (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Gin mills in Africa (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Dawn in Africa (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Africans celebrating feast, Maiduguri, Central Africa (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Loose negatives, Africa (Box 4, Folder 27-30)
    - Cape Palmas, Liberia (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Minaret in India (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Loose negatives, Egypt (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Arabs in Sahara, near Egypt/Ethiopia border (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Main street, Asmara, Eritrea (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - African family (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Native woman on Gold Coast (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Liberian Policemen, Monrovia (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Diamond mines, Accra (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Coptic church, built for Moslems by Italians, Asmara (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Native woman pounding fu-fu, Liberia (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Monrovia dock scene (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Native workers, Liberia (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Aerial view of Ivory Coast (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Loose negatives, Africa (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
    - Native kids, Central Africa (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Loose negatives, Africa (Box 4, Folder 48-49)
    - Fauna, Firestone (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Loose negatives, Africa (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Fauna (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Loose negatives, Africa (Box 4, Folder 53-54)
    - Native on bicycle (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Africans dressed in American clothes (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Shirt salesman (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Two village/town scenes (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Three North African soldiers (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Africans pulling in nets (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Misc. military (Box 4, Folder 61-74)
    - Personal army shots (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Plane and plane crash (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - American soldiers in Liberia (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Doctor checking child's spleen (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Boxer (military) (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - US bomber (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Native council with military person (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Military bomber (no photo) (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Soldier and native with machete on termite mound (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Various scenes with soldiers (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Family (not war related) (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Troop ship in Atlantic (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Trees and jungle (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Termite hill, 15' (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Bare breasted Doc with camera (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - NYC scenes (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Beach, boat scene (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - City street scene (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Three snails (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Historic building (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Arabic hotel (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Arabs with donkeys, street scene (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Man with little girl on cobblestone street (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Soldiers mail call (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Soldier on bicycle with chimp (possibly Doc) (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Two soldiers boxing (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - US bomber (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Misc. (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - negatives (4 rolls) of photos, mostly Africa (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Books
    - 'Campaigns of the Conquest of Italian East Africa,' 1942 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 'Tribal Markings and Marks of Adornment of the Africans of the Northern Territories of the Gold Coast Colony,' by Capt. C.H. Armitage, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 'Airway to India,' 1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 'History of Liberia,' by Abayomi Karnga, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 'Tribes of the Ashanti Hinterland,' Vol. I, by Capt. R.S. Rattray, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 'Native African Medicine,' by George Way Harley, M.D., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 'An Elementary Geography of the Gold Coast,' by D.T. Adams, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 'How to Make Good Pictures,' Eastman Kodak Company, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 'Introducing Africa,' by Carveth Wells, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 'Lighting Up Liberia,' by Arthur I. Hayman and Harold Preece, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 'The Belles of Shangri-La,' by George 'Doc' Abraham, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - 'Introducing West Africa,' British booklet, no date (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 'Hunger Fighters,' by Paul de Kruf, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 'What to do Aboard a Transport,' by a Group of Scientists, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 'Psychology for the Fighting Man,' 1943 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 'Guerilla Warfare,' by 'Yank' Levy, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - '36th Field Artillery,' Fort Bragg, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 'Sex in World War II,' video of History Channel program, 2002 V-1450
  - Films
    - Large Film Reel, Africa (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Small Film Reel, Africa (unidentified) (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Film Reels, Africa (unidentified) (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Film Reels, Africa 1943-44 (Box 6, Folder 3-5)
    - Film Reels, Africa 1944 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
    - Film Reels, Accra (Ghana) (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
    - Film Reel, Red Sea (Eritrea) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Film Reels, Africa (unidentified) (Box 7, Folder 1-9)
  - CDs
    - Abraham Cornell African Archive introduction CD-335 (Box 3)
    - Abraham Cornell African Archive CD-336 (Box 3)
  - DVD's
    - George 'Doc' Abraham WWII Africa Archives DVD-211 (Box 3)
- Series II. Gardening
  - Clippings, correspondence, photos and slides, Green Thumb articles, and personal files
    - Clippings and photocopies of articles about Doc and Katy (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Awards given to Doc and Katy (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - General articles, 1960-1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - General Articles, 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - General Articles, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - General Articles, 1990-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Clippings and photocopies of newspaper articles (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
    - Christian Science Monitor columns (Box 8, Folder 10-16)
    - Misc. News clippings and Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 17-19)
    - Misc. News clippings (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Clippings and Correspondence Regarding the cancellation of the Green Thumb radio show, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Press clippings and Correspondence, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - News clippings and Correspondence, 1980's (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Misc. News clippings and Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 24-25)
    - Correspondence with J. Robert Nuss, Penn State College of Agricultural Sciences (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Misc. News clippings and Correspondence, dust jackets for Green Thumb book (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Teaching materials, Community College of the Finger Lakes (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Country Woman Magazine, articles and correspondence (Box 9, Folder 3-6)
    - Country Woman Magazine, misc. (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
    - Nursery Retailer, Q&A (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Articles from the Tribune-Democrat, Rochester, NY, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Chestnut Tree article by Doc, Tribune-Democrat, Rochester, NY (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - "Ground cover beets weeds" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - "How to grow the world's largest pumpkin and squash" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - "Gardening is the biggest hobby" article (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Green Thumb quiz for kids (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Green Thumb question of the week - geese (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - "Easter lilies trumpet the season" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - "How to identify garlic" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - "Gardening for fragrance" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - "Gardens and your septic system" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Questions and answers about wood chips (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Weather and the garden, by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - "Take care to water new trees" by Doc Abraham, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - "Wildflowers for landscape use" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - "Walnut trees zap others" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - "Walnut toxicity" by Doc and Katy, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - "Tropical hibiscus" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - "How to control fruit pests in the home orchard" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - "Homemade sprays to fight insects and disease" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - "How to cope with tree damage" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - "Treated wood harmful" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - "Toxic mulch" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - "Storing tomatoes" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - "Rooting hardwood cuttings" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - "How to get rid of fleas, ants, mice...etc." by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - "New Years Resolutions, 1987" (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - "How to reflower the florist chrysanthemum" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - "Tips on making a raised bed" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - "Your kitchen is a garden center" by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Articles by Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Misc. clippings by and about Doc and Katy, 1961-2001 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - "Green Thumb" articles (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Various issues of the "Naples Record" 1996-2005 with articles about Doc and Katy (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - "Thank you" notes from Naples Central School, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Garden Writers Assoc. of America award, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Various "how to" articles by Doc and Katy, 2000-2005 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Agreements and contracts for "Belles of Shangri-La" from Vantage Press (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence with Vantage Press regarding "The Belles of Shangri-La" (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Articles about Africa by George Abraham for the "Cornell Countryman," 1943 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Incomplete manuscript of "The Belles of Shangri-La" (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Misc. garden advice articles by Doc and Katy, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - The Green Thumb Question Box (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Cornell Univ. publications about Doc and Katy, Outstanding Alumni award, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence with Cornell Agriculture, Plantations, and Ornithology, 1971-2000 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Cornell Plantations and Ornithology publications (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence with Cornell president Frank Rhodes, 1988 regarding environment curriculum (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Photograph, Cornell 45th year reunion (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Hobby Greenhouse Association correspondence and articles, 1978-2001 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence with Margaret Herbst Public Relations, 1977-78 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Misc. articles and correspondence, 1970's (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Society of American Florists (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Green Thumb praise (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Green Thumb column promotion (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Geneseo curriculum (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Doc and Katy nature trail dedication (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - All American Nurserymen (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Radio show scripts, late 90's-2002 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Doc and Katy radio show transcripts (Box 12, Folder 22-26)
    - Funny stories (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - General articles by Doc and Katy (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - WHAM, Doc and Katy radio show scripts, 1990-2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - General letters (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Lonsberry-Doc articles (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Modern Maturity (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Literacy volunteers (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Obituaries and memorials (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Poems (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Prentice Hall correspondence (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Rotary volunteer projects (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Rodale Press correspondence (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Teaching children gardening (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Misc. correspondence to Doc and Katy (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
    - Misc. letters (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Article query, correspondence (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Thank you letters (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - "Why the Green Thumb clicked" by Doc (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Misc. manuscripts for Green Thumb column (Box 13, Folder 20-21)
    - Manuscripts of various Green Thumb question box columns (Box 13, Folder 22-25)
    - Manuscripts, 1994-98 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Garden Myths debunked (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
    - Manuscript to Luke Miller at Better Homes and Gardens (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Unpublished manuscript on gardening for Family Fun Magazine (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Unpublished manuscript, "Kitchen is your garden center" (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
    - Misc. letters (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Retirees gardening (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Handwritten manuscript by Doc (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - House plants (Box 14, Folder 11-12)
    - Prentice Hall correspondence (Box 14, Folder 13)